Damn it.
Where did those chickens go?
They couldn't have gotten far
in this downpour...
I'm gonna find them,
no matter what.
And get more footage
that goes viral, for sure!
I'll definitely become
a successful Viewtuber!
No... I need to become one!
That's right...
I haven't forgotten
the humiliation from then...
THREE MONTHS AGO
Hey, Ibokura!
The Chief was furious!
Can't you write a proper report?
There's no way anyone can
read this. Am I right?
We had to rewrite it.
Aren't you gonna thank us?
You did that all
of your own volition.
I don't owe you any thanks.
What did you say?!
Are you messing with us?
I'm not messing around at all.
Don't bother with him.
He doesn't have the decency
to express any gratitude.
All he has going for him is pride,
even though his work's sloppy.
That's right.
You might catch his incompetence.
I hope he quits soon.
Loser.
Salary leech...
Those pieces of–!
I'm gonna show each and
every one of you!!
I'll become a big,
successful viewtuber...
And I'll show those scum!
That's why I need to
find those chickens!!
Chickens!!
EPISODE 6
BUILT LIKE A BRICK COOP
This is not good!
Are you okay, Grandpa?
I'm finally feeling a bit better...
I hope the Mister is okay.
I'm worried.
I'm continuing my travels alone.
Did he really go off on his own?
Everybody!
Please stay calm and listen...
What is it?
- What happened?
- What?
We've received word
from the state office.
Due to getting 1000 milliliters-plus
of rainfall last night...
There are fears that
Kurome Dam could collapse.
What?!
What does that mean?
The water in the reservoir
is going to flood the town!
What?!
You're kidding!
How could a dam that big
break so easily?!
Actually, this reminds me...
Back when the dam was first built,
there was a rumor
that the dam was built cheaply
and it caused a stir.
You're kidding me!
Those scumbag builders!
What should we do?!
The state office told us to
continue taking shelter here.
That's ridiculous!
If all that water in
the dam floods,
the whole town would
be submerged!
We have to get out of town quickly!
There's still a storm outside
and the river is flooding.
We can't leave town right now.
What are you doing?
Trying to find a route to the dam.
DAM
If we go there, there might be a way
to prevent it from breaking.
Wait!
I'm going too!
Where did they go?
It's that chicken!
But I don't see the other one!
No, I can't be picky right now.
I gotta go after them.
That dam's gonna break!
Where should we go?!
Crap! Where are they headed?!
I see the dam!
Is that a Demon?
Why is that Demon...?
Oh, I get it!
Where did Elizabeth and Piyoko go?
Everyone, look!
It's a Demon!
A Demon's about to break the dam!
What? Are you serious?!
First, a flood, now a Demon?!
Connect to the TV!
Aren't Demons those
monster-like creatures?
INPUT 2
It's on!
You're right, it's a Demon!
Gimme a break!
It's over!
No, look closer.
I think that Demon's trying to
prevent it from collapsing.
INPUT 2
What?!
You're kidding...
No, it's true!
That Demon's holding it up!
- What?!
Hang in there.
- Hang in there, Demon!
- Please!
- Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Elizabeth and Piyoko?!
What are they doing there?!
This is incredible!
The viewers keep pouring in!
What are you doing?!
It's dangerous here!
Get out of here right now!
You're a Demon, right?
Why are you doing this?
I...
I want to save all the townsfolk!
Save... humans?
Just keep on living.
You'll stumble upon
your purpose soon enough.
Keiji, I've found it.
I've always wanted
to be useful.
I finally realize that now.
Keiji, now I can hold
my head up high and say this...
This...
This is the reason I was born!
I'll hold this dam up even
if it costs me my life!
You all need to get out
of here quick!
What a kind Demon.
I've only read about this online.
So... demons like this
really do exist!
I'm going to exterminate
the Demons.
Does this mean... I was wrong?
Elizabeth!
Look!
A human?!
What's he doing here?
Why?
What's with this guy?
Why is he going this far
just to help humans?
He's throwing his life on the line...
Why?
I could never...
Mom...
I want to become a lawyer.
I want to help lots of people in need!
PASS THE EXAM
REJECTION NOTICE
I failed because of you, Mom...
It's all your fault, Mom!
I realized I was blaming everyone
around me for my problems...
But deep down... I knew.
I was the one who was
responsible for everything.
I just didn't want to admit it.
Mom... I don't...
I don't wanna die...
I don't wanna die!
Keiji!
Mister!
That rooster... saved me?
Keiji!
Did you come because you were
also worried about the dam?
To think you were the one keeping
the dam from breaking, Morio!
Look at me, Keiji!
I'm protecting everyone in town!
I had a reason to live after all!
That's right.
Without you, there would have
been many casualties.
No doubt, you're a hero.
M-Me? A hero?
Those words are wasted on me...
I just wanted to be useful.
That's just like you.
I'm... at my limit!
Morio!
Morio...
This is bad!
Over here, Elizabeth!
Both of you, get somewhere safe!
What about you, Keiji?!
I'm going to stop the flood!!
- What?!
It really collapsed.
This can't be...
No way...
Honey...
Dear Lord in heaven...
I'm scared!
No way...
- It's okay...
- Are we going to die?
Are they running away?
No.
I can't imagine they would
turn a blind eye to this...
They probably have
some sort of plan.
I have to follow them!
I did what I could.
I hope I was useful to somebody.
Keiji...
Thanks to you,
I gained confidence in myself.
I'm really glad I met you.
Thanks a bunch, Keiji.
I'm really glad I was born.
I'm really glad...
Morio...
Those feelings that
you risked your life on...
I won't let them go to waste!
Kokekokko!
What are you doing, Keiji?
I knew it!
That rooster!
I've seen him on Viewtube!
Me too! It's the rooster
who defeated the Demon!
You think...
...he's trying to stop
the flood waters?
That must be it!
He must be trying to save us!
Please stop the water, Rooster!
Please, Rooster!
Is he a friend
of Elizabeth and Piyoko's?
- He made a wall!
Please hold!!
No way...
It can't be...
A little wall like that won't cut it.
I need something sturdier!
Something sturdier!
That's it!
He's so fast!
What? Is he making another wall?
It's not going to hold!
But we're already so close to town!
We need to stop it here, or else!
Oh, I get it!
That boulder!
What?!
He's going to drop that boulder
and block the water's path!
A mass of rock that big
should withstand the water.
Amazing... He's a genius!
I see, he's going to bring it down.
But isn't it too big?
Will he make it in time?!
Hurry, Keiji!
The water's here!
Keiji!
Mister!
Keiji...
Hang in there, Mister!
Hang in there...
Hang in there, Rooster!
Hang in there!
We're counting on you, Rooster!
Please, Mr. Rooster...
Hang in there!
This is just like the day we met.
You didn't know us,
but you saved us.
It seems you're the kind of man
who can't help
but rescue those in need.
I finally realize it now!
That I...
Love you!
What?!
I'm not done yet!
Is that the spot?!
Keiji!
Mister!
You're kidding...
No!
Mister... the Mister is...!
What's that?
N-No way...
Super Kokekkoko!
He stopped it.
How dare they make such
a crummy dam.
It really makes my crown curl
Morio... We stopped it...
It's stopped!
We're safe!
Honey!
Yeah.
Thank you, God,
thank you, Buddha,
Rooster! Rooster!
It's a good thing
we let him get away.
Yeah...
Elizabeth, Piyoko,
Mr. Rooster...
Thank you for saving us.
I promise to become a great doctor.
So one day,
I can help lots of people,
just like you did.
Be well, my chicken friends.
Misuzu! Come over here!
Oh, okay!
Mister!
Great job!
I love you!
What?!
Uh, Piyoko...
Don't you think
that's enough kissing?
What's wrong with me wanting
to kiss my own husband?
Did you say "your husband"?
I think you might be the only one
who thinks that.
By any chance, Elizabeth...
...are you falling in love with him?
That's silly!
Why is this child so perceptive?
Then why are you blushing?
It's weird!
You're imagining things!
Liar!
I'm not lying!
You were!
No, I wasn't!
Cut the racket.
Mom?
It was a bad storm.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm fine.
So... I've decided to continue traveling
for a while.
Viewtube?
I realized it wasn't my calling.
Yeah.
I'm totally sure.
While traveling, I want to confront
my insecurities head-on...
...to become a strong person.
Yeah. I'll call you again soon.
Talk to you later.
Hey, Rooster... I'm gonna change.
I'm gonna become someone who
can protect people just like you.
Rooster... Demon...
I can say it earnestly now...
Thank you for helping me
realize everything!
By the way, Keiji...
I thought you only cared
about avenging Sarah.
How did you end up here?
ONE HOUR EARLIER
Something feels completely off.
Hurry!
- The dam is going to collapse!
- Be careful!
The dam is collapsing?
Does that mean this town
will get submerged?
Keiji!
Mister!
I'll never find them in time.
In that case...
I'll have to stop the flooding!
I was just passing by, that's all.
You're such a bad liar.
Morio...
He was a kind Demon.
I guess Demons like him actually
existed...
I said once before that I wanted
to eliminate all Demons,
but I take that back.
The sake we shared was the best.
Farewell, Morio.
What?
I'm alive?
I'm alive!
Look at how resilient I am!
Huh? Wait,
why's the floodwater stopped?!
It was Keiji!
Hey!
Morio?!
It's the kind Demon!
Keiji!
That son of a bitch is still alive!
You stopped the flooding, right?
Thank you!
Come visit again!
I'll treat you to
some fresh sea urchin!
Let's drink some more sake again!
Yup! Let's meet again!
There they go.
Who... Who are you?!
Keiji's going
on a group date?
I hope he'll be okay...
What do you do
on a "group date"?
Well, uh...
Next time:
Crowing Over a Feather
You just changed the subject!
- Tell me what it is!
- I don't know!
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS